[both laugh]
（两人笑）
- Okay, I'll go first.
好的，我先来。
My super sleepover secret is...
我的超级睡衣派对秘密是...
Until I was seven, I had a crush on Smokey the Bear.
直到我七岁，我暗恋过斯莫基熊。
- You know he's a cartoon, right?
你知道他是卡通人物吧？
I mean, that's cool if that's what you're into.
我的意思是，如果你喜欢那也没关系。
- Come on, he's cuddly,
拜托，他很可爱，
he cares about the environment
他关心环境
and how cool does "Mrs. Dawn the Bear" sound?
而且“熊夫人黎明”听起来多酷？
Okay, tell me your deep, dark secret.
好了，告诉我你的深藏不露的秘密。
- I can't. I don't really feel comfortable.
我不能。我真的感觉不舒服。
- I promise, whatever you say does not leave this room.
我保证，无论你说什么都不会离开这个房间。
- Totally. My lips are sealed.
绝对保密。我守口如瓶。
- Do you mind? - Not at all. I love secrets.
你介意吗？一点也不。我喜欢秘密。
How about you?
你呢？
- I'm all ears. And biceps.
我洗耳恭听。还有，我的二头肌也很期待。
Time to work the glutes.
是时候锻炼臀肌了。
- This is ridiculous. - Just ignore them.
这太荒谬了。别理他们。
[toilet flushes]
（马桶冲水声）
- Ooh-hoo!
哦吼！
Ooh, sorry about that. Nature called.
哦，抱歉打扰了。自然召唤。
And let's just say she had a lot to talk about.
这么说吧，她有很多话要说。
- How am I supposed to ignore that?
我怎么能忽视那个呢？
It's not that bad. Here. Let's paint our nails
其实没那么糟糕。来，我们涂指甲
and forget they're here.
然后就当他们不在。
- Gotta chalk up for the three-pounders.
得为三磅重的家伙准备粉笔。
- Dicky! What are you doing?
迪基！你在干什么？
- I wanna look good in my dreams.
我想在梦里看起来好看。
And yours.
还有你的。
- [giggles] Still not that bad.
（咯咯笑）还是没那么糟糕。
- Uh-oh! Nature's calling back.
哎呀！自然在召唤。
- It's that bad.
确实很糟糕。
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
一二三四！
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
呐呐呐呐呐呐
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！♪
- Good morning.
早上好。
Would you and Mae like some breakfast?
你和Mae想吃早餐吗？
- I would, but Mae left hours ago.
我想吃，但Mae几个小时前就离开了。
Right after the boys used her toothbrush
就在男孩们用她的牙刷清洁耳朵之后。
to clean out their ears.
亲爱的，很抱歉他们又毁了一个睡衣派对。
- Honey, I'm sorry they ruined another sleepover.
不仅仅是睡衣派对，妈妈。
It's not just the sleepovers, Mom.
我得在被子里穿衣服，
I have to get dressed under the covers,
他们有一面鼻屎墙，还有那些气味，妈妈。那些气味。
they have a booger wall,
他们还有鼻屎墙，
and the smells, Mom. The smells.
还有那味道，妈妈。那味道。
I can't take it!
我受不了了！
- Well, you could have your own room.
- 嗯，你可以有自己的房间。
- No! I want my own room! And I'm not taking--
- 不！我想要自己的房间！而且我不会再忍受——
wait, what?
等等，什么？
- Yes, I've been thinking about it,
- 是的，我一直在考虑，
and you should have your own room.
你应该有自己的房间。
- What's the catch? - No catch.
- 有什么条件吗？ - 没有条件。
- Can I also have a pony? - No.
- 那我还能养一匹小马吗？ - 不行。
- Eh, worth a shot.
呃，试试也无妨。
I can't believe I'm getting my own room!
我简直不敢相信我会有自己的房间！
I can't believe I'm getting my own room! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
我简直不敢相信我会有自己的房间！谢谢你，谢谢你，谢谢你！
Honey, you're a girl, you need space
亲爱的，你是女孩，你需要空间
to do girl stuff. Especially in this house
去做女孩的事情。尤其是在这个家里
with all these boys hanging out everywhere.
到处都是这些男孩子晃来晃去。
- Hey! - Oh!
嘿！
What are you doing up there?
哦！
- I went up to clean the vents, but I discovered a whole new world up here.
你在上面做什么？
Hey, remember that hamster we lost?
我上去清理通风口，但我发现了一个全新的世界。
I kinda found it.
我好像找到了它。
- Dad, I'm getting my own room! - That's great!
爸爸，我要有自己的房间了！那太好了！
Are you gonna put her in the coat-slash-vacuum room?
你打算把她放在大衣间还是吸尘器间？
- That's a closet. - Oh, well, the only other room
那是个衣橱。哦，好吧，家里唯一的另一个房间
in the house is my train room.
是我的火车模型室。
[gasps] Monster!
[惊呼] 怪物！
- Tom, you know, our daughter is a young woman.
汤姆，你知道，我们的女儿已经是个年轻女性了。
Her body is gonna start changing--
她的身体即将开始发生变化——
- ♪ La, la, la, la! ♪
♪啦，啦，啦，啦！♪
- Besides, you're hardly ever in your train room.
而且，你几乎不在你的火车模型室里。
I think you've outgrown them.
我想你已经长大了。
- ♪ La, la, la, la, ♪
啦，啦，啦，啦，
[grunts]
（咕哝声）
"It's crazy to have a trampoline floor," you said.
你说“有个蹦床地板太疯狂了”。
You must feel pretty ridiculous right now.
你现在一定觉得挺尴尬的。
I'm calling the trampoline guy on Monday.
我周一就给蹦床师傅打电话。
Have you guys ever seen my happy dance?
你们见过我的快乐舞吗？
No?
没有？
Well, it goes a little something like this.
嗯，大概是这样的。
♪ Dawn's getting her own room! ♪
Dawn有自己的房间了！
♪ Dun dun dun dun dun duh! ♪
♪ 咚咚咚咚咚咚！ ♪
- I don't understand why she gets her own room.
- 我不明白为什么她有自己的房间。
- Why not me? - Why not me?
- 为什么不是我？ - 为什么不是我？
- Both excellent questions,
- 这两个问题都很好，
but have you considered, why not me?
但是你有没有想过，为什么不是我？
- Face it, boys, I'm a young woman now.
- 面对现实吧，男孩们，我现在是个年轻女性了。
Pretty soon, my body's going to go through changes--
很快，我的身体会发生一些变化——
all: ♪ La, la, la, la! ♪
大家：♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦！ ♪
- So will yours. All: ♪ La, la, la, la! ♪
- 你的也会。大家：♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦！ ♪
All: Whoa, whoa, whoa!
大家：哇，哇，哇！
- What do you think you're doing?
- 你以为你在干什么？
I'm taking Sprinkles to my new room.
我要带小彩星去我的新房间。
- No, you're not. Dad spent five hours
- 不，你不能。爸爸花了五个小时
and $300 winning him at the fair for all of us.
和300美元在集市上赢了他，为了我们所有人。
- Get him!
- 抓住他！
- Oh, please. You guys could care less
- 哦，拜托。你们根本不在乎
about Sprinkles.
小彩星。
You're just jealous of my new room.
你们只是嫉妒我的新房间。
- Maybe we are, maybe we're not.
- 也许我们是，也许我们不是。
But either way, you're not taking him!
但无论如何，你不能带他走！
You ruined him!
你毁了他！
- Come on, let's go to our new home...
- 来吧，我们去新家...
Sprinkles' neck.
小彩的脖子。
- Good luck. You'll never make it without us.
- 祝你好运。没有我们，你永远做不到。
- You'll never make it without me.
- 没有我，你也永远做不到。
- We don't need a girl in here. We're mature, manly men.
- 我们不需要一个女孩在这里。我们是成熟的男人。
- Spider. [all scream]
- 蜘蛛。[所有人都尖叫]
- I think I'll be fine.
- 我想我会没事的。
♪ Ra-ta-ta-ta-ta ta! ♪
♪ Ra-ta ta-ta-ta ta! ♪
- Presenting, for the first time ever...
My own room!
I call it, "Aloha-dorable."
I love it! It's boy-free, chalk-free...
[sniffs] Ah, and odor-free.
- And check this out, now that I don't have bunk beds, I can do this.
We are going to have so much fun in here.
I'm already planning a sleepover for the weekend and--
- I'm scared of balloons!
- You're scared of what?
- Balloons.
气球。
It was my super sleepover secret
这是我那晚超级睡衣派对的秘密。
from the other night.
从那天晚上开始。
Phew.
呼。
Feels good to get that off my chest.
说出来感觉真好。
- This is so great-- not the weird balloon thing,
这太棒了——不是那个奇怪的气球事情，
but the fact that you can share it.
而是你能分享这件事。
This is a total safe zone.
这里绝对是个安全区。
- Welcome to your new room! - [screaming]
欢迎来到你的新房间！
- Get them out. Get them out!
把它们弄出去。把它们弄出去！
- Sorry, Mom. I'd explain,
对不起，妈妈。我本想解释，
but it's a girl secret.
但这是个女孩子的秘密。
- Ooh! Girl secrets! Me first!
哦！女孩子的秘密！我先来！
Okay! I have a crush on a boy named Dad.
好吧！我暗恋一个叫爸爸的男孩。
- What's happening?
发生了什么？
- Isn't it great that the three of us gal pals
我们三个好姐妹终于有了一个地方可以聚聚，
finally have a place to hang?
这难道不是很棒吗？
- The three of us?
我们三个？
- Oh, you're right. The four of us.
哦，你说得对。是我们四个。
- Say hello to her royal highness,
向她尊贵的高贵公主问好，
Princess Giggles.
笑笑公主。
- When I was your age, she spent every night with me.
我像你这么大的时候，她每晚都陪着我。
And if I was ever feeling sad,
如果我感到难过，
I would just press her tummy and--
我就会按她的肚子然后——
[doll giggles]
[玩偶发出笑声]
- I've been saving her for you,
我一直为你留着她，
and now that you've got your own room, she's all yours.
现在你有了自己的房间，她完全属于你了。
- Really? Thanks, Mom. - Aww.
真的吗？谢谢妈妈。 - 哎呀。
Hey gang, I found these in the hall--
嘿，伙计们，我在走廊里找到了这些——
- [screaming]
[尖叫声]
- I know, I know, it's a chick room.
- 我知道，我知道，这是女孩的房间。
I'll just put these right here and shut the door.
我就把这些放在这儿然后关门。
- [shrieking]
- [尖叫]
- I have a vision for Dawn's empty space...
- 我对Dawn的空房间有个想法...
And industrial-size pants press.
还有工业尺寸的裤子熨斗。
Say goodbye to wrinkles and hello to success.
告别皱纹，迎接成功。
- Or something real!
- 或者来点实际的！
Octopus hair stylist!
章鱼发型师！
With a blow dryer in every arm.
每只手臂都带着吹风机。
- Think, Dicky. That's ridiculous.
- 想想，Dicky。那太荒谬了。
We don't have eight outlets.
我们没有八个插座。
- Solar powered octopus hat.
太阳能章鱼帽。
Problem. Solution.
问题。解决方案。
- While you guys bicker, I'm a man of action.
你们还在争论的时候，我是个行动派。
It's meat o'clock, boys, and I'm buying.
现在是吃肉时间，伙计们，我请客。
- It's weird, but I like it.
虽然奇怪，但我喜欢。
I'll grab some plates.
我去拿些盘子。
Who needs plates?
谁需要盘子？
We have hands!
我们有手啊！
We should've replaced Dawn with meat years ago!
我们早该用肉替换掉Dawn的！
- Uh-huh!
嗯哼！
- First night in my own room.
在我自己的房间的第一晚。
With my Mommy right next to me.
妈妈就在我旁边。
- Aloha.
阿罗哈。
Did you know "aloha" also means "goodbye"?
你知道'阿罗哈'也意味着'再见'吗？
- Look at you, all grown-up and knowing stuff.
看看你，都长大了还知道这么多东西。
You know what else I know?
你知道我还知道什么吗？
The boys want you to go and tuck them in.
男孩们想让你去给他们盖被子。
- No way!
不可能！
This is our special girl time!
这是我们特别的女孩时间！
It's time to dish. I'm sure the boys are fine.
是时候聊聊了。我相信男孩们没事。
- [all groaning]
- [大家都在抱怨]
- I can't believe we ate the whole thing.
- 真不敢相信我们把整盘都吃光了。
- [sniffs]
- [嗅了嗅]
My sweat smells like gravy.
我的汗闻起来像肉汁。
- My stomach kept saying "Stop,"
- 我的肚子一直在说“停”，
but the meat kept saying "Go!"
但那肉一直在说“继续！”
[all groan]
[大家都在抱怨]
- Ooh, I just thought of another secret!
- 哦，我刚想到另一个秘密！
Okay. I used to have this John Stamos pillowcase
好吧。我以前有个约翰·斯塔莫斯的枕套
and I would snuggle with him, like, every night.
我每晚都会抱着他，就像，“甜美的梦，Jesse叔叔。”
I'd be all, "Sweet dreams, Uncle Jesse."
我会说，“甜美的梦，Jesse叔叔。”
and then I would--
然后我就会——
- Okay, that sounds like
好的，听起来像是
a "night two" kind of secret.
那种适合“第二晚”的秘密。
- All right, you're right.
好吧，你说的对。
We'll save it for tomorrow night.
我们留到明晚再说。
Aw. My little girl isn't so little anymore.
哎呀。我的小女儿不再那么小了。
Sweet dreams.
做个好梦。
- Thanks again, Mom. I love my new room.
再次感谢，妈妈。我喜欢我的新房间。
- Me too.
我也是。
- Finally. No annoying brothers,
终于。没有烦人的兄弟，
no over-sharing mother, just me and you, Sprinkles' neck.
没有过度分享的母亲，只有我和你，Sprinkles的脖子。
Alone in my own room.
独自在我的房间里。
I didn't think it would be this quiet.
我没想到会这么安静。
Or dark.
或者这么暗。
[wood creaking] [wind whistling]
（木头吱吱作响）（风呼啸）
- Or shadowy.
或者这么阴暗。
Be glad you don't have any eyes, Sprinkles' neck.
幸好你没有眼睛，Sprinkles的脖子。
[squeaking] Or anything to pee out of.
（吱吱声）或者任何可以排尿的东西。
Ooh! Okay, don't freak out.
哦！好吧，别慌。
Princess Giggles!
吉吉公主！
Maybe your laughter will help us feel better.
也许你的笑声能让我们感觉好些。
[doll giggling]
（玩偶咯咯笑）
[sinister laughter]
（阴森的笑声）
[alarm clock ringing] - [screams]
（闹钟响） - （尖叫声）
- Oh, it's morning.
- 哦，天亮了。
We made it! We made it, Sprinkles' neck.
我们做到了！我们做到了，斯普林克尔的脖子。
- Kids! Breakfast!
- 孩子们！吃早餐了！
Tom, you're a grown man playing with children's toys,
汤姆，你一个成年人玩儿童玩具，
sitting crisscross applesauce in the middle
坐在厨房中间的crisscross applesauce姿势。这太荒谬了。
of our kitchen. It's absurd.
嗯，如果你看到火车如何以复杂的方式与它们的环境和彼此互动，
- Well, you wouldn't think it was absurd
你就不会觉得这荒谬了。
if you watched the complex ways
这实际上是一种艺术形式。
in which the trains interact with their environment
观察。
and each other.
早上好，Caboose博士。
It's an art form really.
那么，向你道早安，
Observe.
火车头前校。
Good morning, Dr. Caboose.
要去磨坊加满吗？
Well, good morrow to you,
colonel Front-Of-The-Train.
火车头上校。
Going to fill up at the mill?
要去磨坊加水吗？
Why yes. Care to join me?
是的，愿意一起吗？
All aboard!
全体上车！
[blows whistle]
[吹哨]
See?
看吧？
- Tom, I'm gonna be very clear about this.
- 汤姆，我会说得很清楚。
I have never been less attracted to you.
我从未对你这么不感兴趣。
- Got it. I'll just pack these up
- 明白了，我这就把这些打包
and donate them to the trainless.
然后捐给没有火车的人。
- Dawn? - I love my room!
- 黎明？ - 我爱我的房间！
- Yeah, yeah, rub it in.
- 是啊，是啊，炫耀吧。
- Hey, honey, how was your first night in your new room?
- 嘿，亲爱的，你新房间的第一晚怎么样？
Mom, I'm going to be totally honest.
妈妈，我要完全诚实。
The thing is, I--
问题是，我——
I should've moved into my new room years ago!
我早该几年前就搬进新房间的！
What's up, former roommates?
怎么了，前室友们？
You mean "room-meats."
你是说“房间肉”。
[all laughing]
[大家都笑了]
I--I don't get it.
我——我不明白。
- You wouldn't. It's an inside joke.
你不会懂的。这是我们内部的笑话。
As in inside our room that you no longer sleep in!
就像在我们那个你不再睡的房间里的内部笑话！
- Whoo! - Boom!
哇！
Both: Ha!
嘭！
- Oh, well, my room's got jokes, too.
哈！
Knock-knock, who's there? Not you!
哦，好吧，我的房间也有笑话。
What! Hoo!
敲敲门，谁在那儿？不是你！
- Are you okay?
什么！哇！
- [yawning] I'm fine, why?
你还好吗？
- Because when you're tired, you imagine your dog can talk.
我没事，怎么了？
By the way, you know what would be a good smoothie flavor?
顺便问一下，你知道什么会是好的冰沙口味吗？
Dog butt.
狗屁股。
[sneezes]
（打喷嚏）
- I love my room!
我超爱我的房间！
- Dawn, what's going on with you?
Dawn，你怎么了？
- You know my new room that I love so much?
你知道我那个我非常喜欢的新房间吗？
- Yeah. - I hate it!
嗯。
It's dark and shadowy
我讨厌它！
and that doll's freakin' me out, Mae.
那里又黑又阴暗，
[boys chattering, laughing]
还有那个娃娃让我毛骨悚然，Mae。
- Plus, now my brothers have all these inside jokes.
而且，现在我哥哥们有了这些内部笑话。
What's "room meat," Mae?
什么是“房间肉”，Mae？
[whispering] What is "room meat?"
[低声]什么是“房间肉”？
- Look, Dawn, if you're this unhappy,
听着，Dawn，如果你这么不开心，
just move back in with them.
就搬回去和他们一起住。
- No way, if I move back in, it's admitting defeat.
不可能，如果我搬回去，那就等于承认失败。
They said I couldn't make it without them.
他们说我离开他们就活不下去。
Quick. They're looking at us.
快点，他们在看我们。
Pretend we're having fun.
假装我们在玩得很开心。
[girls laugh loudly] - Oh, my...
[女孩们大声笑]哦，我的...
- Wow!
哇！
- Wow! Dawn seems happy.
哇！Dawn看起来很开心。
- She's supposed to be miserable without us.
她应该没有我们很痛苦才对。
- I mean, we're happy without her,
我是说，没有她我们很快乐，
but we're not that happy. Are we?
但我们也没那么快乐。对吧？
- Of course we are.
当然我们很快乐。
Remember "room meats"?
记得“室友肉”吗？
- Eh.
呃。
- It's getting a little old.
这有点过时了。
- Maybe she doesn't need us.
也许她不需要我们。
- Well, we don't need her.
好吧，我们不需要她。
Quick, pretend we're happier than she is.
快，假装我们比她更开心。
[boys laughing loudly]
[男孩们大声笑]
- Oh, that's so funny!
哦，太好笑了！
- Here we are. Back again.
我们又回来了。
Creepy tree,
诡异的树，
creepy doll.
诡异的娃娃。
I can do this.
我能做到。
I'll show those boys who's strong enough to live alone.
我要让那些男孩看看，谁有足够的力量独自生活。
- Good night, honey. - Mommy! Come on in!
晚安，亲爱的。 - 妈妈！快进来！
- Are you ready for night number two?
- 你准备好迎接第二个夜晚了吗？
- Not without some girl chat.
- 没有女孩间的聊天可不行。
So tell me about this Dad guy you have a crush on.
那么告诉我，你对那个叫Dad的家伙有好感是怎么回事？
- That's really sweet, but I know you're not
- 那真是太甜蜜了，但我知道你其实并不那么感兴趣，所以，晚安！
really that interested, so, good night!
- 等等！你还没告诉我你和Jesse叔叔的枕头故事呢。
- Wait! You never finished telling me
- 你知道的，我明白这里发生了什么。
about you and Uncle Jesse pillow.
- 哦，我真高兴。
- You know, I know what's going on here.
- 你需要你的空间，你想让我离开这里。
- Oh, I'm so glad.
- 亲亲，晚安！
- You need your space and you want me out of here.
- 哦！阿罗哈！
[smooches] Good night!
晚安！
Oh! Aloha!
哦！阿罗哈！
- [squeaky] I'm scared.
我害怕。
- [pounding]
砰砰声
That's good. Creepy ceiling noises
这很好。天花板的怪声
are distracting me from the other creepy things.
让我分心，没那么害怕其他怪事。
And they're getting louder.
而且声音越来越大。
And closer.
越来越近。
Come on, Sprinkles' neck! Run!
快点，Sprinkles的脖子！跑！
- [pounding gets louder]
砰砰声更大了
- [screams, groans]
- [尖叫声，呻吟声]
- [screaming]
- [尖叫声]
- It's me! It's me!
- 是我！是我！
- Dad?
- 爸爸？
Sorry, you scared me.
对不起，你吓到我了。
What were you doing up there?
你在上面做什么？
- The--
- 那--
inspecting the vents.
检查通风口。
[boys laughing loudly]
[男孩们大声笑]
- The boys sound like they're having a ball, huh?
- 男孩们听起来玩得很开心，是吧？
- Yeah. A lot of laughing.
是的，笑声很多。
- Wait, I can see something's bugging you.
等等，我看得出你有些心事。
- You can?
你能看出来？
- A father knows when his little girl isn't happy.
父亲知道他的小女儿不开心的时候。
And I think I know how to fix it.
我想我知道怎么解决。
- You do?
你知道？
- Keep it down in there!
在那边小声点！
Your sister's trying to sleep!
你妹妹正试着睡觉呢！
- Oh, well. At least you're not in the vent.
哦，好吧。至少你不在通风管道里。
It is so loud. It's like being in the room with them.
那里太吵了。就像和他们在一个房间里一样。
And that is the last thing you want, am I right?
这就是你最不希望的事情，对吧？
- Yeah, last thing.
是的，最不希望的事。
- Excellent parenting, Tom.
汤姆，真是出色的父母之道。
- It's official. I hate the sound of laughter.
正式宣布，我讨厌笑声的声音。
- Let's just turn it off already.
我们干脆把它关掉吧。
- No!
不！
We have to drown out the sound
我们必须用声音淹没我们不断争吵的声音。
of our constant arguing.
我们的争吵并没有那么频繁。
- It hasn't been that constant.
是的，有！
- Yes, it has. - No, it hasn't!
不，没有！
- You guys are fighting about fighting!
你们俩在争论谁在争论！
- No, he's fighting about fighting! - Are you really gonna fight with me
不，是他在争论谁在争论！
about who's fighting about fighting?
你真的要和我争论谁在争论谁在争论吗？
- This is all Dawn's fault.
这都是Dawn的错。
If she was here, we'd be fighting with her
如果她在这里，我们会和她争吵而不是彼此。
and not each other. - Maybe we could ask her to move back in.
也许我们可以请她搬回来。
- No! We're not admitting defeat.
不！我们不是在承认失败。
- [sighs]
叹气
- Dawn's gone, Nicky.
Dawn已经走了，Nicky。
We just have to learn to enjoy fighting with each other.
我们只能学会享受彼此争吵。
- You know what you should learn?
- 你知道你应该学什么吗？
How to clean up that meat spit!
如何清理那肉渣！
- Dicky don't do dishes!
- 迪基不做洗碗的活！
- Dicky don't do English either!
- 迪基英语也不行！
- Dicky don't like your tone! - Can we please argue
- 迪基不喜欢你的语气！ - 我们能不能用第一人称争论？！
in first person?! - Dicky don't know what that is!
- 迪基不知道那是什么！
- They never laughed like that when I lived with them.
- 我住在他们那里时，他们从没那样笑过。
You hear this?!
你听到了吗？！
Of course you don't. You don't have any ears!
当然没有。你没有耳朵！
- Hi! - [screaming]
- 嗨！ - [尖叫]
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- What are you doing up here?
- 你在这里做什么？
- I asked you first.
- 我先问你的。
I'll honor that.
我会尊重这一点。
But you have to promise not to tell Ricky and Dicky--
但你必须答应不告诉Ricky和Dicky--
- Tell me what? [both scream]
- 告诉我什么？[两人尖叫]
- Dicky! What are you doing up here?
- Dicky！你在这里做什么？
- I was just, uh...
- 我只是，呃...
Looking for Nicky.
在找Nicky。
Found him!
找到了！
All right, see you guys in the morning.
好吧，明早见，伙计们。
And don't tell Ricky I was up here.
还有，别告诉Ricky我在这儿。
- Too late. [all screaming]
太迟了。
- Well, well, well,
哎呀，哎呀，哎呀，
look what we have here.
看看我们这儿有什么。
What do we have here?
我们这儿有什么？
- Looks like we have you crawling in the direction
看来我们抓到你朝我们房间爬去。
of our room.
而你朝
- And you crawling
我房间爬去。
in the direction of my room.
朝我的房间爬去。
All: Huh.
所有人：嗯？
[train whistle blaring]
[火车汽笛声]
I'm sleep-deprived, but does anybody else hear that?
我睡眠不足，但有人听到那个声音吗？
- Sounds like Colonel Front-of-the-Train!
听起来像是火车前部的上校！
- That's what dad was doing up here!
那就是爸爸在这里做的事！
[train chugging] - It's getting closer!
[火车轰鸣声] - 它越来越近了！
- Follow me!
跟我来！
- Wait, we're not all gonna fit!
等等，我们不可能都挤得下！
- Dicky don't wait!
迪基别等了！
- Ow! [all groaning]
- Back up!
- Dicky can't move!
- We're doomed! - No matter what happens,
I want you to know, I was scared without you.
I miss you! - You do?
- I miss you, too. - I wish you never moved out.
- We're a mess without you.
- What about the laughter? - Faked it.
What about your laughter?
- Faked it. I love you guys!
- 假装笑的。我爱你们！
All: We love you, too. [train whistle blaring]
所有人: 我们也爱你们。[火车汽笛声]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Huh. - That wasn't so bad.
- 嗯。- 那还不算太糟。
[cracking] [all screaming]
[破裂声] [所有人尖叫]
- Now that was bad.
- 现在那真的很糟。
- Oh, my gosh! My babies!
- 哦，天哪！我的宝贝们！
- My babies!
- 我的宝贝们！
Chug to me.
快来我这里。
I think you can, I think you can.
我想你能行，我想你能行。
- Tom! Your kids just fell out of the ceiling.
汤姆！你的孩子刚从天花板上掉下来了。
- Well, your kids just broke my train.
嗯，你的孩子刚刚弄坏了我的火车。
- Which you said you were donating to the trainless.
你说过你要捐给没有火车的人的。
- Well, I--this is not the time, Anne.
嗯，我——现在不是说这个的时候，安妮。
Our kids just dropped out of the ceiling!
我们的孩子刚从天花板上掉下来了！
Now what were you kids doing up there?
你们这些孩子在上面做什么？
And why did you take my trains up there with you?
还有，你们为什么要带上我的火车上去？
- We were admitting we missed each other.
我们承认我们想念彼此。
- And Dawn's moving back in.
而且Dawn要搬回来了。
- Right? - Yeah, right?
对吧？ - 对，对吧？
- Well, I do miss you guys, but...
嗯，我是挺想你们的，但是...
I think I should tough it out in my own room.
我觉得我应该在自己的房间坚持下去。
- I'll honor that.
- 我尊重你的决定。
- Well, if you ever need anything,
- 好吧，如果你有任何需要，
we're right across the hall.
我们就在走廊对面。
- Actually there is one thing.
- 其实还真有件事。
Finally, I feel like I'm gonna get
终于，我觉得我能睡个好觉了。
a good night's sleep.
谢谢你们。
Thanks guys. - No prob, sis.
- 没问题，姐妹。
- We got your back.
- 我们挺你。
- Nothing to be scared of now.
现在没什么好怕的了。
- Don't tell Mae, but this is the best sleepover ever.
别告诉Mae，但这是我经历过的最好的睡衣派对。
Good night.
晚安。
- This room's great.
这房间真棒。
- Yeah, I don't know what she's so scared of.
是啊，我不知道她在害怕什么。
- Just some shadows and this cute little doll.
就是一些影子和这个可爱的小玩偶。
[sinister laughter]
[阴森的笑声]
[boys whimpering]
[男孩们呜咽]
- [snoring]
[-打呼噜]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- [cheerful melody]
- [欢快旋律]
- ♪